Principal's Office
Tachibana-san, you're a pop idol, right?
I think I've seen you on TV...
I'm a model, sir.
I just got back from filming overseas.
Oh, my apologies.
I still can't believe a famous model like
yourself would come to our school.
It's a good school, sir.
Super old, though.
Huh?
I hate you and I hate manga!
And I spotted the guy I hate.
Cosplay Group Potential?
M-Mikarin!
Holy shit, it's Mikari Tachibana in the flesh!
Her legs are so long!
And she's so cute!
Like, inhumanly cute, honestly.
M-Mikarin, could I get your autograph?
Dude, what's wrong with you?!
Of course! Anyone else want one?
Wait, really?!
I do!
Me too!
She's so nice.
Bet she's 'nice' to everyone.
Heard she's dating that male model Kei-kun.
Lucky her.
Not surprised. With her looks and body,
she could have any guy she wanted.
Hey, do you guys have a manga club?
A manga club? Anyone know?
Wait, you like manga? Me too!
Nope, I hate manga.
It was an act of God.
Just an accident.
Calm down, just act like it never happened.
Manga Club
I hope she's not here already...
Oh, Senpai!
Um, uh...
This is so awkward...
I gotta break the silence!
My heart's still racing...
Am I still sick?
Hey, uh, sounded like something
big went down this morning.
Oh, yeah, a new student joined our class.
She's some famous model.
A model? Huh.
Yeah, she's a model.
A-and she's really cute!
Wow, didn't think you cared about that kinda stuff.
She's got the perfect looks and body to
cosplay as Lilie's best friend, Miriella!
Oh. That's what you cared about.
I could make a legendary ROM if I got her to join me!
Oh, right!
I found this in here!
Yeah, that belongs to the club.
I remember my senpai taking pictures with it.
Apparently, it's a good model!
It turned on!
There are still pictures on it.
These must be from the Culture Festival.
Didn't know he was snapping pics here.
I-I'm sorry!
Huh? For what?
I keep making all these demands of you.
What do you want to do, Senpai?
I'm ready for anything!
What'll it be today? Anime? Video games?
Club's all about having fun together!
Nah...
Let's take some pictures.
Last time was my first time taking cosplay pictures,
but it was kinda fun, I guess.
And you looked really...
Your cosplay looked really good.
Hello?!
I'm just so happy!
So those are happy tears?!
I thought I was forcing you to
go along with all my silly ideas...
I was so worried you didn't want to do any of it...
I wouldn't do it if I didn't want to...
So hearing you want to do it makes me super happy!
Huh?
I'm gonna get changed!
Hold it!
Teachers were inspecting bags today so
I didn't bring my cosplay.
Wow, too bad.
We can take pictures another time.
Wait!
Senpai, come with me!
Huh?!
Okay, why this random classroom?
Cause no one's gonna come in here!
Let's take some practice shots in here!
You mean, like, just in your uniform?
Yep!
And this 50 mm fixed
lens should work for us.
We'll just leave it in P-mode for now.
What am I getting all worked up for?
I'm just taking pictures of Ririsa.
She's not Liliel!
How do I look?
I dunno, but I took a bunch...
W-well?
That bad?!
I look horrible...
Oh, sorry! The pictures are fine.
I know we have to practice,
but I just hate seeing pictures of myself...
They look fine, though.
Cause I'm not Liliel,
and I wish I could be her.
Sorry.
I know you wish I were 2D, too.
I mean, school uniforms are all over the place in manga.
This is 2D enough.
You're so smart, Senpai!
Wait, I am?
I see it now!
I just need to pretend this uniform is cosplay!
What?
This is gonna be perfect!
Manga-length skirt!
Glasses, off!
A touch of makeup!
H-how about now?
Do I look like a manga character now?
T-this is Ririsa, remember?!
She's not Liliel!
She's 3D, she's 3D, she's 3D...
Is that helping him focus?
But this pose is too normal.
I should go for a sexy manga pose instead.
Whoa! No, her underwear's part of her costume!
It's totally normal!
Is it, though?!
Not good enough...
The ecchi manga I like gets sexier than this!
I gotta live up to its standards!
Where'd my glasses go?
The clumsy glasses girl!
That's definitely a manga cliché!
Next up...
Owie!
Maybe it wasn't acting.
Whoa!
Sorry! I didn't mean to!
This is perfect, Senpai!
What?
This is the kind of fanservice
I see all the time in shonen manga!
She's actually getting this excited
about acting out a sexy scene.
This is what Ririsa likes.
Cosplay is insane...
Senpai!
Let's take a look at those pictures now!
Sure.
They all came out pretty sexy,
just like you wanted.
I forgot I wasn't wearing a cosplay!
Don't look!
W-why?!
These aren't costume panties,
they're my actual panties!
No looking, you perv!
What?!
We got our practice,
so make sure you erase all those pictures!
Okay, sheesh!
Class 1-1, Ririsa Amano,
please come to the faculty office immediately.
Think that's for you?
I totally forgot I had mandatory tutoring!
I'm gonna be in so much trouble!
Her grades are already that bad?
Sorry, Ririsa.
DELETE PHOTO?
Club's all about having fun together!
But I've gotta keep pictures of fun club activities.
What's Mikarin doing in the club building?!
Is she gonna join a club?!
Which one?
Can I get a picture?
Sorry, no pictures!
Hey, I just said no pictures...
Excuse me, I need to get through!
Sorry, let me through!
Please stop pushing!
Move, please!
I need to get through here!
Out of the way!
I'm sorry! Are you okay?!
I'm so sorry!
Wait up, Mikarin!
Hanging out alone in here's just not as fun.
How'd I have so much fun in here by myself before?
Mikarin!
What the...
Manga Club
Manga...
Senpai?!
Wait, Mikari?
S...
Senpai!
I found you.
5 years earlier
Okumura-senpai!
Senpai, do you have a crush on anyone?
I sure do!
I'm in love with Liliel!
She'll never betray me, not ever!
You stupid, weird otaku!
I hate you and I hate manga!
It's been too long.
Mikarin!
I thought she came this way!
Mikarin?
Mikarin!?
I don't see her anywhere, though.
Did you hear something?
W-what's going on?
I haven't seen you since we went
to different middle schools.
Mikarin!
Did she go home?
This is crazy.
I can't believe you're the famous
model who just started today.
Please, I'm not that famous.
Thanks for rescuing me, though, Senpai.
There's one thing I still don't get.
Why'd you hug me all of the sudden?
Sorry, I couldn't help it.
I was kinda hoping I'd make your heart skip a beat.
What?!
Wait, why are you soaking wet?
It's a long story.
Can I stay here till my clothes dry off?
Yeah, sure.
Even my bra is all wet.
This is the super cute one I wore just for you, too.
Wh- you can't be serious!
Sure you don't wanna see it?
S-stop messing around and
put your stupid underwear on!
Okay, I'm good.
You can turn around now.
Whoops, maybe I wasn't good.
W-would you stop messing with me?!
What? It's not like I have a change of clothes.
I'm still tired from my late-night shoot yesterday,
so I'll take a nap while I wait.
Okay, fine, but put some clothes on.
Wanna join me?
Okay, that's enough!
Why are you doing this?!
Cause you never treated me like
a cute girl when I was a kid,
and teasing you is really fun.
Bet you think I'm cute now, huh?
I dunno. You've always been cute, Mikari.
Huh?!
Wait, really?!
Yeah?
Everyone said she was cute back then, too.
Not like that! I'm different now!
I got way cuter, and way more fashionable,
and now I'm a famous model!
I'm not a little kid anymore!
The way you're fiddling with your pigtails...
You're not that different.
You're still the little kid I played with back then.
I am not!
You're naked, you're naked!
S-sorry!
Wait!
Don't go, Senpai.
I've been waiting forever to have you this close.
That took forever!
I hope Senpai is still here.
Can we stay like this just a little longer?
There's no way he doesn't get tempted now...
Wait, Senpai! I'm not... I'm not ready to go that far!
You wanna do
it at school?!
You're gonna catch a cold like that.
I stepped right on this doujin, too...
Forgive me, Liliel.
He's a lost cause.
Hey, Senpai.
Do you have a crush on anyone?
Like, a girl?
Senpai?
Yeah.
I'm in love with Liliel, of course!
And I'll never cheat on her!
Ririsa's face popped into my head,
but that's only because I thought of her Liliel cosplay!
Which means everything is fine!
Nothing is wrong!
Weirdo otaku.
You haven't changed at all.
I'm happy to see you, but I still hate you.
What...
Why was Mikari crying?
Why can't I just tell him I like him?
My life would be so much easier if I hated him.
I should've known he wouldn't change his
mind when he found out I was a supermodel.
You interested in showbiz?
A girl with your figure could kill it as a model.
You could be the cutest one out there.
If I got cuter, and got popular...
Great! You're looking hot!
Then maybe Senpai will like me!
Perfect!
Mikari-chan, I heard you've got
a crush on a boy at your school?
Huh? Yeah.
But, he doesn't feel the same way.
Uh-huh.
He's just some random student, though.
I mean, yeah.
And he's a weird, creepy otaku, too.
So why him?
When you get famous,
you could be with an actor or a famous singer.
Forget about him.
Forget about him?
Look at the wild caveman!
Stop it!
So much hair!
It's so weird and fluffy!
Stop it!
Lord Ashford commands you!
Get your hands off my Liliel!
Eww, it's Yuckymura!
Run! You'll catch his nerd cooties!
It's Liliel! She's from this manga!
Children's Park
Wanna play?
Why? Who are you, even?
C'mon, lemme play.
No way!
Lord Ashford commands you!
I know that manga!
You from around here?
You're cute.
Run, Liliel!
Yes, Ashford-sama!
Oh, no!
Yuckymura!
Everyone falls in love with me the second they see me,
but not Senpai.
He hasn't changed since the day I fell in love with him.
I could've forgotten about him if he'd changed, but...
Mikari-chan?
No.
If I betrayed him now,
I'd be no better than the 3D girls he hates.
Huh? 3D what?
He's been betrayed over and over again.
That's why he's so devoted to Liliel.
So I'm never going to betray him!
If he only trusts an angel,
then I'll become that angel for him.
I'll work hard so that one day,
he turns towards me and finally
says the words I want to hear...
One day... One day...
I haven't seen him in years,
but I'm still head over heels.
I guess I'm a little relieved he hasn't changed.
He's still the guy I love,
and no one's gonna take him from me.
How am I gonna get through
to that stubborn otaku, though?
Oh, Senpai! I can see him from here! Nice!
Who's SHE?!
I'm so sorry about this!
Don't apologize, your timing was kinda perf...
I mean, don't worry about it!
Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything's fine.
Then let's get back to taking pictures!
Can you stop randomly stripping?!
And I thought you didn't have your cosplay!
I remembered I brought a spare
costume to school, just in case!
In case what?!
Why would you ever need it?!
My makeup's not perfect,
but it'll work for some test shots.
Yeah, it doesn't have to be perfect.
Senpai?
Se...
Senpai, you liar!
You said you wouldn't cheat on Liliel!
So what's this?!
And why are you blushing
like that in front of her?!
Wait, hold on...
Senpai, do you know her?
You stay out of this!
You're in my class though, right, Tachibana-san?
Will you cosplay with me?!
What?
Are you Liliel?
Lili x Miri